A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Log Files (Grant and Project Proposals) FA734
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1981
  - L81-66: Williams College: Technical Assistance to Botswana, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-67: Ford Foundation: Agriculture and Rural Development in Latin America and the Caribbean, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-68: Ford Foundation: Legal aid program in Egypt, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-70: The Translation Center: Black Writers of Africa and America, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-71: University of the Academy of Christian Humanism: Research and teaching of Human Rights, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-73: Instituto Latino Americano de Doctrina y Estudios Solicale, Santiago, Chile: To develop a new graduate program in economics, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-76: International Institute for Strategic Studies (IISS): 1982 Annual Meeting on impact of military and strategic expenditures on the economy, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-77: Center for US/European/Middle East Cooperation: Pursuit of Middle East Peace, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-80: International Peace Academy: Middle East Conflict Resolution, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-82: Ford Foundation: Information log on OXFAM-America Press Seminars, 1981 (Reel L-453)
  - L81-83: Ford Foundation: Child Development/Child Care, 1981 (Reel L-454)
  - L81-85: Ford Foundation: The foundation membership in the New York Regional Association of Grant Makers, 1981 (Reel L-454)
  - L81-86: Inter-American Policy Group: Conference on US policy towards Latin America, 1981 (Reel L-454)
  - L81-87: University of Southern California: To develop a manual concerning the general linear model application and illustrations from developing nations, 1981 (Reel L-454)
  - L81-88: Institute for Advancement of Legal Aid: Funds to expand their human rights and legal literacy work, 1981 (Reel L-454)
  - L81-90: International Water Resources Assn.: Special session of their 4th World Congress, 1981 (Reel L-454)
  - L81-91: Brookings Institution: Evaluation of the National Security Studies component of Brookings Institution, 1981 (Reel L-454)
  - L81-94: Enterprise for Cooperation Toward Development: Rural action research in Norte del Cauca, 1981 (Reel L-551)
  - L81-101: Council on Religion and International Affairs: Seminar on global depression or a new international economic order, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-103: Ford Foundation: Rural America program explorations, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-104: African/American Labor Center: Support of Black Trade Unions in South Africa, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-105: Stanford University: Comparative labor law program, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-108: Columbia University: Family planning methods and infertility risk in Thailand, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-109: National Womens Conference Center: Delivery system for achieving goals of the women's movement, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-110: American-African Education Foundation: To educate Black South Africans in the US, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-111: Ford Foundation: United fund for international economics, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-112: Ford Foundation: United States/ Mexican relations, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-117: Georgetown University: Soviet strategy in Latin America and its political impact, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-119: Yale University: Edit a Black Encyclopedia, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-120: California Rural Legal Assistance Foundation: Information log on the organization, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-121: Hudson Institute, Inc.: Comparative Strategic Culture, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-123: Ford Foundation: Information Log on video display terminals, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-124: University Research Association: Receive Latin American scholars interested in basic research and associated technologies, 1981 (Reel L-539)
  - L81-125: Johns Hopkins University: Project on East/West Security in the 1980's, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-131: Ford Foundation: Outreach programs in the Peoples Republic of China, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-132: Ford Foundation: Consultative group on international agricultural research, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-133: Ford Foundation: Miscellaneous proposals for International Affairs office, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-136: Ford Foundation: Women and Pensions, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-139: Ford Foundation: Information log on child survival and fair start, 1981 (Reel L-523)
  - L81-139: Ford Foundation: Information log on child survival and fair start, 1981 (Reel L-525)
  - L81-139: Ford Foundation: Information log on child survival and fair start, 1981 (Reel L-526)
  - L81-139: Ford Foundation: Information log on child survival and fair start, 1981 (Reel L-527)
  - L81-139: Ford Foundation: Information log on child survival and fair start, 1981 (Reel L-528)
  - L81-139: Ford Foundation: Information log on child survival and fair start, 1981 (Reel L-529)
  - L81-139: Ford Foundation: Information log on child survival and fair start, 1981 (Reel L-530)
  - L81-139: Ford Foundation: Information log on child survival and fair start, 1981 (Reel L-531)
  - L81-140: Ford Foundation: International Affairs -New Delhi, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-142: Brookings Institution: Study of the formation of economic policy, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-143: Ford Foundation: Research on the quality of military personnel and the willingness of Blacks to fight in certain third world constituencies, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-149: Bio- Energy Council: Develop bibliographic and other materials on bio-energy technologies, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-150: Institute of Agricultural Economics: Organization of the National Agricultural Economics Institute, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-151: The University of East Anglia: Course on agricultural research planning, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-154: Ford Foundation: International Water Management Project, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-157: The Pennsylvania State University: Conference in Taiwan, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-161: National Center for Atmospheric Research: Research on flood warning systems in India, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-162: Resources for the Future, Inc.: Exploring and developing petroleum resources in Non-Opec developing countries, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-164: Princeton University: Nuclear Arms Control, 1981 (Reel L-464)
  - L81-166: Agricultural Marketing Project: Fight rural poverty in Tennenesse and the South-East, 1981 (Reel L-464)
- 1982
  - L82-1: Vienna Institute for Comparative economic Studies: Clearinghouse for Polish Professionals, 1982 (Reel L-551)
  - L82-5: Ford Foundation: Immigration, 1982 (Reel L-463)
  - L82-7: Overseas Development Council: Evaluation of Activities of the Overseas Development Council, 1982 (Reel L-463)
  - L82-8: Ford Foundation: Inquiries on 1982 Ford Foundation awards for non-fiction books offering humanistic perspectives on major contemporary issues (Reel L-463)
  - L82-12: Children's Hospital National Medical Center, Washington, DC: Establish a newborn and infant developmental assessment training program, 1982 (Reel L-463)
  - L82-15: Ford Foundation: International Relations - Developing Countries, 1982 (Reel L-463)
  - L82-16: Ford Foundation: Study of Washington D.C. Arts Consortium, 1982 (Reel L-455)
  - L82-17: Oak Ridge Associated Universities, Inc.: Study of a 2nd Nuclear Era in the U.S. in the 1990's, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-18: American Academic Association for Peace in the Middle East, NYC: General Support, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-19: Eisenhower Foundation for the Prevention of Violence: General Support of their programs, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-23: Family Focus, Inc., Illinois: Community Drop-In Centers for Teenagers (especially pregnant teenagers), 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-26: Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Women Science and Technology, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-27: Council on economic Priorities: Waste and Accountability in Defense Spending, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-28: Battelle Human Affairs Research Center, Washington, DC: Development Implications of Refugees in the Horn of Africa, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-29: University of North Carolina: Large Scale Longitudinal Study of Infant Feeding Practices in Developing Countries, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-30: Vanderbilt University: Establish a Program of Research on State Government and Human Services, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-31: New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center: Develop new programs and expand and improve existing programs on preventive actions, parental concerns and better health., 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-32: Program for Appropriate Technology in Health (PATH), Seattle, WA: Program in four Asian countries for safe and effective use of oral rehydration solutions., 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-36: Accounters Community Center, Illinois: Establish a family/infant cooperative health station., 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-37: Modern Times, Inc., Md: Developing and producing plays on abortion., 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-39: University of Texas System Cancer Center: Biochemical characterization of inhibin from follicular fluid and LH, RBI from corpra lutea., 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-42: International Food Policy Research Institute: Nutrition-related policy research, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-43: Watts Labor Community Action Committee: Preventive service expansion in day care facilities, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-44: Chulalongkorn University, Thailand: Role of U.S. and Japan in the A.S.E.A.N. region, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-45: Family Focus, Illinois: Establish a national grass roots family service organization called Family Focus U.S.A., 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-47: South Central Mississippi Rural Health, Inc. Association: Project - Adolescent Health - Low Income Black Mississippi Youth, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-58: Scientific Committee on Problems of the Environment, Colorado: Preliminary explorations of a number of problems involving the global environment, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-59: Resources for the Future, Inc.: Water assessment research and food and agricultural policy program, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-62: Bank St. College of Education: Effect of budget cutbacks on family life, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-63: American Indian Lawyer Training Program: Symposium on Indian water rights, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-67: Johns Hopkins University: Epidemiologic study of predictors of ovulation in lactating women, and study of children exposed to hormonal contraception in utero and study of health care utilization within the home, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-69: Ford Foundation: International Affairs/ Indonesia, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-70:: Political crisis on Africa's Islamic frontier: Islam, Communism and the West, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-72: Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Manuscript on the conference on security and cooperation, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-77: Ford Foundation: Information log on possible future Ford Foundation actions in Poland, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-78: Phelps-Stokes Fund: Scholarship program for African refugees, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-79: Mid-West Universities Consortium for International Activities, Inc.: Training an consultation with the International Agricultural Research Centers, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-82: Columbia University: Political economy topics, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-85:: Third World Non-Governmental Organizations - untapped potential, 1982 (Reel L-456)
  - L82-89: Women's Research and Education Institute: Information resource on women's issues for the congresswomen's caucus, 1982 (Reel L-551)
  - L82-93: National Hispanic Center Advanced Studies and Policy Analysis: Chicano leadership training program, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-96: Federated Union of Black Arts, Johannesburg, South Africa: To help the F.U.B.A. achieve its goals, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-103: Columbia University: Development and population law and policy program, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-104: Columbia University Center for the Study of Human Rights: Women's rights project, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-106: Business and Professional Women's Foundation, Washington, DC: Information Log, 1982 (Reel L-551)
  - L82-108: Ford Foundation: Education and culture planning meetings, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-110: Aman Folk Ensemble, Los Angeles, CA: Support for dance touring company, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-112: Ford Foundation: Rockefeller - Mellon - Ford Foundation reproductive science competition, 1982 (Reel L-459)
  - L82-112: Ford Foundation: Rockefeller - Mellon - Ford Foundation reproductive science competition, 1982 (Reel L-460)
  - L82-112: Ford Foundation: Rockefeller - Mellon - Ford Foundation reproductive science competition, 1982 (Reel L-461)
  - L82-112: Ford Foundation: Rockefeller - Mellon - Ford Foundation reproductive science competition, 1982 (Reel L-466)
  - L82-112: Ford Foundation: Rockefeller - Mellon - Ford Foundation reproductive science competition, 1982 (Reel L-467)
  - L82-112: Ford Foundation: Rockefeller - Mellon - Ford Foundation reproductive science competition, 1982 (Reel L-468)
  - L82-113: Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, NY: Project - facilitation of a comprehensive Middle East peace, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-117: National Lawyers Guild - Puerto Rico Legal Project: Civil Rights litigation activities, 1982 (Reel L-551)
  - L82-118: Ford Foundation: International security and arms control education, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-121: Legal Aide Foundation of Colorado: Provide civil legal assistance to low income residents of Colorado, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-122: Ford Foundation: Reproductive health group on teenage pregnancies, 1982 (Reel L-551)
  - L82-125: Council of Foreign Relations: The widening Atlantic: core issues in European American relations, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-126: Chilean Human Rights Commission: Support for commission's programs, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-127: Ford Foundation: Conference What do women want? Writing, reporting, editing and broadcasting about women and women's issues, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-133: Mississippi Action for Community Education, Inc.: Program for low income teenagers, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-136: Princeton University: Research on international monetary system, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-144: Ford Foundation: International grant making, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-147: The Twentieth Century Fund, Inc.: Study on Foundation performance, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-148: Ford Foundation: Paper by Enid Schoettle on International Peace, Security and Arms Control, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-150: Piact (Program for the Introduction and Adaptation of Contraceptive Technology): Measurement of the incidence of abortion - related mortality in Nepal, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-156: University of Natal, South Africa: Support for the Institute of Natural Resources, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-157: Market Theatre Foundation, South Africa: Development of their arts complex, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-159: Southern Rural Alliance, Georgia: Increased political participation, governmental responsiveness, and economic development in the rural deep south, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-160: New York University: Research on the economics of the performing arts in the 1970's and 1980's, 1982 (Reel L-457)
  - L82-163: National Legal Aid and Defender Association: Minority bar involvement program, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-164: Stanford University: Publication of special issue of SIGNS: Journal of women of culture and society on the subject of women's poverty, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-165: Johns Hopkins University: Case control study to identify risk factors for low birth weight and prenatal deaths in Natal, northeastern Brazil, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-167: Ford Foundation: Research competition in international peace, security and arms control (see PA 85-411 and PA 85-0087), 1982 (Reel L-468)
  - L82-167: Ford Foundation: Research competition in international peace, security and arms control (see PA 85-411 and PA 85-0087), 1982 (Reel L-469)
  - L82-167: Ford Foundation: Research competition in international peace, security and arms control (see PA 85-411 and PA 85-0087), 1982 (Reel L-470)
  - L82-167: Ford Foundation: Research competition in international peace, security and arms control (see PA 85-411 and PA 85-0087), 1982 (Reel L-471)
  - L82-167: Ford Foundation: Research competition in international peace, security and arms control (see PA 85-411 and PA 85-0087), 1982 (Reel L-472)
  - L82-167: Ford Foundation: Research competition in international peace, security and arms control (see PA 85-411 and PA 85-0087), 1982 (Reel L-473)
  - L82-171: Ford Foundation: Background log on reproduction issues, 1982 (Reel L-569)
  - L82-171: Ford Foundation: Background log on reproduction issues, 1982 (Reel L-570)
  - L82-171: Ford Foundation: Background log on reproduction issues, 1982 (Reel L-571)
  - L82-171: Ford Foundation: Background log on reproduction issues, 1982 (Reel L-572)
  - L82-171: Ford Foundation: Background log on reproduction issues, 1982 (Reel L-573)
  - L82-174: International Centre of Theatre Research, France: To design a production of the Maha-Bharata project, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-175: Northwestern University: Evaluate the effectiveness of expanded pre-natal service with the community - outreach in reducing infant mortality and morbidity, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-176: Ford Foundation: Youth employment and training for business organizations, 1982 (Reel L-551)
  - L82-183: Skid Row Development Corp.: Provide transitional housing for indigents, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-185: National economic Development and Law Center: Legal and planning assistance to Title VII community development corporations on an ongoing basis, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-187: Santa Barbara Community Housing Corp.: Provide affordable housing to law and middle income families, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-188: Volunteer Urban Consulting Group, NYC: Non-profit leadership seminar series, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-190: South Bronx Two Thousand Local Development Corp.: Provide construction, management assistance for business and residential improvement in Belmont and East Tremont sections of South Bronx, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-192: Ford Foundation: New York City Office of the Mayor, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-196: Ford Foundation: Information log on older women's programs, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-198: San Bernardino West Side Community Development Corp.: Community economic development activities, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-200: United Neighborhood Houses of New York, Inc.: Partial support for settlement houses in the N.Y. area, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-202: Educators for Social Responsibility: Funding for national office/children's concern regarding nuclear war, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-204: University of Michigan: College in Black and White: Black student experiences on white and black campuses, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-211: Ford Foundation: Meeting with Van Leer Foundation on deprived preschool children, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-214: Regional Plan Association: Seed money to help launch their N.Y. Urban Region economic Information Service, 1982 (Reel L-458)
  - L82-214: Regional Plan Association: Seed money to help launch their N.Y. Urban Region economic Information Service, 1982 (Reel L-462)
  - L82-217: Ford Foundation: Emerging Community Development Corp. (see PA 88-369), 1982 (Reel L-551)
  - L82-219: Ford Foundation: Information on women in Middle East and Asia, 1982 (Reel L-462)
  - L82-227: Ford Foundation: Background log on federation for American immigration reform (FAIR), 1982 (Reel L-462)
  - L82-231: Ford Foundation: Community Foundation collaborative effort on teenage pregnancy, 1982 (Reel L-462)
  - L82-234: Stiftung Weissenschaft und Politik: European/American relations and third world conflict areas, 1982 (Reel L-462)
  - L82-235: Robert B. Choate and Associates: Through educational techniques/communicate to conservative, traditional men about the change in women's lives, 1982 (Reel L-462)
- 1983
  - L83-12: Ford Foundation: Emerging Community Development Corporations for the Denver Area, 1983 (Reel L-490)
  - L83-13: Ford Foundation: Emerging Community Development Corporations for the New York City Area, 1983 (Reel L-490)
  - L83-14: Ford Foundation: Emerging Community Development Corporations for the Chicago Area, 1983 (Reel L-490)
  - L83-15: Ford Foundation: Emerging Community Development Corporations for the Baltimore Area (see PA 84-0076), 1983 (Reel L-490)
  - L83-16: Ford Foundation: The Brain Drain into the U.S. of scientists, engineers and physicians, 1983 (Reel L-490)
  - L83-17: Youth Knowledge Development Project: Evaluation of computer assisted educational programs, 1983 (Reel L-490)
  - L83-18: Ford Foundation: Population Program Review, 1983 (Reel L-490)
  - L83-30: Ford Foundation: 1983 evaluation of Africa related U.S. institutions (Reel L-476)
  - L83-30: Ford Foundation: 1983 evaluation of Africa related U.S. institutions (Reel L-477)
  - L83-36: Ford Foundation: Background on national service for youth services, 1983 (Reel L-521)
  - L83-37: Euro-action, Nairobi, Kenya: Development of Sablaale community program, 1983 (Reel L-476)
  - L83-40: University of Washington: To improve the performance of minority undergraduates in science: the application of mathematics to physics, 1983 (Reel L-476)
  - L83-45: International Center for Monetary and Banking Studies (Switzerland): General information log, 1983 (Reel L-476)
  - L83-47: Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development, Paris, France: International Campaign of Youth Unemployment, 1983 (Reel L-476)
  - L83-47: Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development, Paris, France: International Campaign of Youth Unemployment, 1983 (Reel L-491)
  - L83-48: Ford Foundation: Neighborhood Security and Crime Prevention, 1983 (Reel L-491)
  - L83-49: Ford Foundation: Immunization of children worldwide, 1983 (Reel L-491)
  - L83-61: Organization of American Historians: Improving the instruction of American history, 1983 (Reel L-539)
  - L83-63: Brookings Institution: Symposium on U.S. foreign policy: International broadcasting and crisis management, 1983 (Reel L-492)
  - L83-65: Georgetown University: Hemispheric migration project, 1983 (Reel L-492)
  - L83-66: CEREP, Inc., Puerto Rico: General support, 1983 (Reel L-492)
  - L83-67: Howard University Press Book Publishing Institute: To support 10 scholarships for 2 years, 1983 (Reel L-492)
  - L83-71: Massachusetts Institute of Technology: Ballistic missile defense in the 1980's and 1990's, 1983 (Reel L-492)
  - L83-75: The Trustees of Purdue University: Conference on the study and teaching of Afro-American history, 1983 (Reel L-492)
  - L83-78: Ford Foundation: General information on Islam, 1983 (Reel L-492)
  - L83-79: Cemi camp, Brazil: Study of the effect of Norplant in postpartum women with hypertension, 1983 (Reel L-492)
  - L83-82: Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education: Minority recruitment in Graduate Education, 1983 (Reel L-492)
  - L83-181: Ford Foundation: Junior High School Math and Science, 1983 (Reel L-496)
  - L83-182: Ford Foundation: Review of the Ford Foundation's external affirmative action policy, 1983 (Reel L-489)
  - L83-182: Ford Foundation: Review of the Ford Foundation's external affirmative action policy, 1983 (Reel L-496)
  - L83-183: Ford Foundation: Non-traditional math teacher training programs, 1983 (Reel L-489)
  - L83-187: Heifer Project International, Littlerock, Ark.: Non-profit organizations devoted to assisting small farmers in U.S. and overseas, 1983 (Reel L-489)
  - L83-188: Center for Cultural and Technical Interchange between East and West, Inc., Hawaii: Participatory rural energy development, 1983 (Reel L-489)
  - L83-193: Harvard University: Conference on Women and War, 1983 (Reel L-493)
  - L83-194: World After Nuclear War, Washington, DC: Conference on long-term consequences of nuclear war, 1983 (Reel L-493)